tversity.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy · TVersity Media Server - Official Site

Thank you for visiting tversity.com (together with all content on the site, subdomains including but not limited to forums.tversity.com and wiki.tversity.com, and other websites operated by TVersity or its affiliates (TVersity) (the Site)). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy (Privacy Policy) explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Use, available at <http://tversity.com/termsofuse>.

**Introduction**

We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information you share with us.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, personal profile, IP address, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information. Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to information available on our Site. However, in order to provide you with the services given under the Site, you may have to create an account (Account) and provide us with your email address, a password that you will use for your Account and other specified information.

If you have an Account you may, if you wish, add more data in association with new sources of content that you wish to add to your media library such as your playlist, your collected deep links, and metatags (Your Profile).

**The Way We Use Personal Information and Anonymous Information**

If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site, then we will use your Personal Information to improve our services to you, to contact you and to identify and authenticate your access to the Site’s services that you are authorized to access.

We may transfer your Personal Information within TVersity or to TVersity’s third-party service providers in order to provide TVersity’s services to You in the most efficient manner. This information may be transferred to other countries around the world.

We may provide Personal Information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

If you choose to make Your Profile public, we may display Your Profile to other users of the Site. If you choose to add additional personal details to Your public Profile, those details will be visible to these users as well. Please note that if you choose to share Your Profile online, you may receive unsolicited messages from other users.

We may also use your email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding our services, or, if you have permitted us to do so, to those of our partners who may have relevant offers. You may choose not to receive email of this type by following the instructions at the bottom of such emails.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, ii) enforce our Terms of Use including investigations of potential violations thereof, iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of TVersity, its users, yourself or the public.

We may use Anonymous Information (as defined below) to improve our services and enhance your experience with the Site and its services. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners, for purposes including, but not limited to, targeting advertisements. Anonymous Information means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of our Site and services, URLs and a user’s playlist.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our Site pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.

**Choice**

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to TVersity. The notices we will provide where TVersity collects Personal Information on the Site should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

**Access/Accuracy**

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, TVersity wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. You may check your profile and add information, delete information or correct any incorrect information.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites**

Our Site may use a reputable third party to present or serve advertisements that you may see at our Site. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

**Children’s Privacy**

The Site is not structured to attract children under the age of 13. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. In addition, for users outside the United States, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age.

**In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**

In the event that TVersity is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used.

**Commitment**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and TVersity’s Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@tversity.com. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

**Your Consent**

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to TVersity’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time, which change will be effective 10 days following the modification. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

Last modified: October 13 , 2009
